skidzopedia.com 2014-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Skidzopedia

**Skidzopedia.com** is committed to protecting your privacy. I only use the information I collect about you to process advertisements and to send you feeds via email, which is automated. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

###  **What information is collected? How do I use it?**

When you apply for an advertisement, I only need to know your name and e-mail address. This allows me to process and fulfill your order. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, I may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so I can administer the contest and notify winners.

###  **E-mail Subscription**

If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail ( powered by Feedburner ), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

###  **Advertisers**

I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the ad companies like Google Adsense, Chitika, and Project Wonderful. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

###  **Links**

Skidzopedia.com also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibliity of the linked site and Skidzopedia has no control or influence over their policies. I encourage my users to check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Skidzopedia cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

###  **Log Files?**

Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

###  **What about “cookies” ?**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My blog uses cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section. **  
**

### **In a NutShell**

Skidzopedia is committed to protecting your privacy. I do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

###  **Questions and Feedback**

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please [send an email](http://www.skidzopedia.com/contact/).
